I'm a faculty member, I'm a tenured professor, and are destroying the campus and undoing a democratic, peaceful protest.
Shame on them. Shame on them.
What department are you in?
I'm in the Global Studies Department.
And why are you here today?
Because we cannot have a genocidal foreign policy in a democracy.
These young people are going to be the ones that have to pay the price for these horrible decisions.
These police officers out here today, that's thousands of students' scholarships.
Thousands of students could have been able to go to school and have books and have housing.
But instead, our chancellor, who is a very cruel man, decided to send thousands of dollars worth of state funding paid for by the taxpayers into the trash.
Are you concerned about this jeopardizing a job?
For real?
What job do I have if the students don't have a future?
It is interesting to hear their perspective, to hear from some of these folks.
Protesting genocide.
Arrested for protesting genocide? Are you a student here?
Arrested for genocide. I am a student.
And why do you feel so passionate to get arrested today?
Because 40,000 people have been murdered in Gaza, there are showing no signs of stopping,
and our university has invested into Black Rock and Black Stone, which are invested...